Devil's dog!
Now you will witness the sword of justice.
Your time has come.
Countless few have triumphed over
countless many. The time has come.
Osman help!
Bala!
Osman
-Bala!
-Help!
Osman! Help!
Hang on.
Give me your hand! Give
me your hand, my daughter!
Come on!
Commander Lukas!
Soldiers, attack!
Come on, this way!
Commander... -Where is Osman?
-He ran away, my Commander.
He ran away?
Let's go after him.
What are we going to do now?
We will do what we need to
do with these swords we have.
We will wash these swords..
...with those dogs' blood.
We cannot let Osman go, Ulugan.
They don't have the chance to leave this place.
Ulugan...
Let's catch Osman.
Osman..
...and his family cannot
run away from us. Altuga.
You will handle these ones.
Come on, let's go to Osman.
Don't let any of them survive, Altuga.
Ilbay...
..you..
...you are a dog who betrays...
...people from your own
blood and your own people.
And from now on...
...you will die as a traitor.
The sultanate of traitors are always destroyed.
That throne...
...will be your nightmare.
Don't worry.
Enough. Soldiers...
...let's cool down these
furious men's fire! Come on!
Allah is the Greatest! Come on!
My Shahzades!
-Bogac, Bahadir. What are you doing here?
We couldn't have waited there
in this hard day, my Shahzade.
Why didn't you stay with our people?
Alps must stand next to their Bey, my Shahzade.
Now the swords will get
stronger with Mongols' blood!
Draw your swords! Come on! Come on Alaeddin!
Come on!
Gonca, are you alright?
Come on my rose. Come on.
Are you alright?
Come on. Come on. Holofira!
Furious boy, here we are
again. But this is the last time.
I will kill you.
I will make your excitement disappear.
With that hole in your hand, who
do you trust to attack me, huh?
We fear none but Allah. We seek
refuge in Allah alone. Now, here, dog...
...now, here, the time for your death has come.
Come on, make your move then.
Brother!
We need to retreat into the forest, come on!
We'll dive into the forest
and split them in two.
Aykurt, Ayaz, we'll go north, come on!
-Nokers (Mongolian Soldiers)!
Attack, come on!
I will rip your heart out!
I will not even let birds and wolves eat it.
Yagiz, Turahan, come with me!
Bahadir, Bogac you two head south quickly.
Come on! Come on!
Go after Alaeddin!
Leave Orhan to me! I will eat him!
Where is Osman?
He ran away.
All these soldiers...
And you let him run away, huh?
He can't get far.
Let's send soldiers after him.
Even if he gets far, Osman
will not leave these lands.
He will face us sooner or later.
Hatun is right.
Osman would never leave these lands.
Nokers(Mongolian Soldiers)!
Search around!
We'll go to the tribe.
We can't leave the tribe
without a leader. Let's go.
Lukas.
Where is Poena? How is she?
I barely escaped death, and
you are asking me about Poena?
Don't worry, she held her
mother's and father's hands and left.
Orhan..
Holofira..
Are you alright? Come. Come.
Are you alright?
I have a headache.
Give some water.
Open your hands.
You are alright? You are.
-I am feeling better.
-Good.
This way!
Orhan.
Orhan, they found us. They are coming!
Move. Move.
Aykurt. -My Shahzade.
No one knows this place better than you.
Now you will take these with you...
...and ride your horse south
to the Black Forest area.
Don't worry my Shahzade.
I will get over them at the
Black Forest God willing.
Okay.
Come on Holofira, come on.
Stop... stop.
So you are going this way, huh?
Nokers(Mongolian Soldiers)! To horses!
Come on!
They've gone.
We can rest a little here.
Then we will keep going.
Holofira.
Are you alright?
As long as you're with me,
...I'm good.
Besides I'm a Kayi girl now.
These trouble can do me no harm.
Beyond being a Kayi girl
...you'll deliver a child for the state.
My lifeful-eyed wife.
Orhan..
Everybody is in terrible situation.
I hope we can get rid of these
troubles as soon as possible.
...so we can revive people's broken hopes.
We will.
For sure, we will.
We should save father first.
Then we all will work together
and turn these fruitful lands...
...into the paradise of the world, God willing.
-Orhan, Mongolians.
-Let's go.
-Brother.
-Big brother.
-Thanks to Allah, you are fine.
-We're good.
The forest is the wolf's home,
brother. Nobody can hurt us here.
-Holofira, are you alright?
-I'm fine. Don't worry.
-Our father is also fine.
-What?
What are you saying? How?
I don't know how.
But they escaped from that dog.
My Allah... Thank You, my Allah.
-Thanks to Allah.
The cryings of the bear called Ulugan
was echoing all around the forest.
We'll skin that bear when it's time, for sure.
We will, God willing.
Osman is saved now and they'll be in trouble.
Yes, they will. Let's go to the hidden place.
My father will be there too.
Let's go.
It looks fine. You're good. You're
stronger than you look, Saruca.
I hit your abdomen and thought you
wouldn't wake up easily. Drink this.
Finish it off.
I thought you'd kill me for a moment.
But you made a good plan not to kill me.
-You hit exactly my abdomen.
-It was a good plan.
You aren't as weak as you look.
Anyway... When you stand
up, I will make you pay.
Yusuf.
How can we deal with those demons?
I'll go back to the tribe.
And keep looking as if I
were taking Ulugan's side.
Take that horse and find Osman Bey somehow.
And tell him I'm loyal to him.
I'll be his eyes in that tribe
and waiting for his orders.
Thank you.
I'm good at tracking.
But how will I deliver the news to you?
Not near the tribe.
Leave a note in this tree's hole.
And I'll take it from there.
Alright?
Come on. Easy. In the name of Allah.
-Here we go. In the name of Allah.
-Come on.
Yusuf.
...it would be easier for you
to win Fatma Hatun's heart.
You missed an opportunity.
I don't like easy races,
Saruca. Don't you know that?
When you restore your
strength, we will compete again.
-Okay.
-Come on!
Welcome!
Osman Bey Secret Tents
This is it, huh?
Father.
Thanks to Allah, you're back.
You're back.
You're back alive, huh?
I'm back, my dear. I'm fine. Don't worry.
-Are you alright?
-I'm good. We're good, father.
As you are here with us now,
all our problems will be solved.
My brothers?
Where are they?
There they are.
-My Bey. -Father!
My sons.
Orhan.
Thankfully, Allah spared your life for us.
-Thank you, thank you. Alaaddin.
-My Bey.
Thanks to Allah.
I feel grateful to my Allah who let me...
...a father to children like you
and a bey to brave people like you!
Thanks to Allah, my Bey!
During my absence
...you never fell into despair.
To able to exist and...
...be united in peace,
...you did whatever should be done to heathens!
Thank you, my people!
Sure, my Bey!
I swear to this glorious flag
that we lost many lives for.
We swear, my Bey!
I swear to mothers whose
eyes are filled with tears...
...and warriors who watered
this holy land with their blood.
We swear, my Bey!
I swear to our cause that we spread all around
the world with the wings of our horses...
...and our faith that is burning
in our chests like a wild fire!
We swear, my Bey!
I swear to this tribe of three tents!
God willing, this place
will be Ergenekon for Kayi!
God willing, my Bey!
The resurrection fire we
build will burn heathens alive!
-Allah is the greatest!
You lost..
...first Osman and then his babies!
You made mistakes one after another, Altuga.
To pay the price of all your mistakes
...you won't wait for meeting Tamu.
You will suffer from Ulugan's
wrath before Erlik Khan's torture.
I'd sacrifice my life for Erlik
Khan and my head for Ulugan.
This fire isn't enough for me.
Cut off my head, Ulugan.
Send me the burning pits of hell.
No. You know, Altuga.
I always give the mistaken a
chance to make up for a mistake.
Nokers(Mongolian Soldiers), extinguish it.
Now get out of my sight.
May you burn in flames forever, dastard!
-Go away, come on!
-Go away!
The mistake you made near the cliff, Lukas.
Altuga isn't the only one
I'm giving another chance.
For your information.
My knights are holding the borders.
I'm ready to help in any way, Ulugan.
Osman can never escape from my land.
Sooner or later, we'll find him.
Until then, we want to stay here...
...and be allies.
Did you bury Saruca, brother?
Don't feel upset.
You did the right thing.
In the name of Allah,
the merciful, the compassionate.
Osman Bey Secret Tents
My Bey.
Thank you, Bala.
This is the best we could make
with things we collect around.
We have little food but it's halal.
Well, we have little food.
But it's blessed.
This affection cannot be found
in any other meals in the world.
My Osman..
Aren't you going to eat?
I am not hungry, my Bala. I am not.
First, our children and our valiants will eat.
No. We cannot do that, father.
You need to gain your strength.
We have a long way to g -Yes.
Yes, look, you didn't even have the table
set up in the tent. It's cold outside.
Eat some, huh?
Bala, in this state, when they are outside...
...I can't sit in a tent. It's better to...
...stay with them.
Alright. Our city is gone.
But our laws will always remain.
We always found what we couldn't find in
palaces, in inns; in the mountains and forests.
Don't worry.
We have the strength to ignite
the fire of resurrection, for sure.
Thank Allah. Thank Allah.
Thank Allah, my Bey. But my Bey...
This treason of Ilbay...
How could such a traitor...
...come from the Kayi, from
us? I can't understand.
If you want to...
...see the real Kayi, look at Ayse.
This is...
...the dagger of my uncle Sungur Tekin.
Here you can see the courage of a child...
...and the symbol of a nation's salvation.
To save me, Ayse gave me this dagger.
Our Ayse has shown with her
heart that she is the child of our tribe.
Right. She did.
Ayse will help and support Ghazi...
She won't leave him alone, right?
She won't, my Hatun, she won't.
Don't worry, we will take Ghazi.
Ghazi will be alright. We will take him.
Right, my Bey? We will take Ghazi.
-We will.
We will take Ghazi and take our state back.
Don't worry.
Now, let's eat our food first.
We need to gather our strength and power again.
Come on. Enjoy.
My Allah..
Let Osman Bey sit on his throne again.
May our state be saved.
And make me a means for
this salvation, my Allah. Aameen.
You beg in vain, Ghazi.
We will never be defeated.
We are the strong ones. Mongols.
Are you strong?
Ulugan uses you. He wouldn't care if you died.
He has no mercy on anyone.
He is not human, uncle. Nor
is anyone who stands by him.
But my Osman Bey is different.
He sees my father and
his Alps like his own brother.
I wish you were one of us, uncle.
I wish you were human.
What we need...
...is not humanity, Ghazi, but strength.
I will never let you...
...be like your father.
-Let go of my hat!
Stop it now.
Take it, you will learn to fight like a Mongol.
It's yours now.
Take it.
Did you think I would become a
Mongol by giving me this sword?
Don't think I'll not point this sword
at you because you are my uncle.
You can point it, of course, you can.
Just don't lose.
If you are carrying my blood, you will not lose.
I know what you are trying to do.
You know I love swords.
My father does not let me
have one because lama child.
You will let me have one and
you will pull me to your side, huh?
You really carry my blood. Really.
Stop it now.
It's not about loving swords.
Let's see if you have talent. Come on.
Allah is the Greatest!
My lion...
Who would have thought
we would be left with so few?
Even if we are few, we
will make everything right.
We will make the Mongols
and the Byzantines kneel.
Yes brother, yes.
Someone's there, brother.
Saruca Bey.
-Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you too.
What happened to you, brother?
I am alright. I am alright, thanks to Allah.
I have to see Osman Bey
immediately. I have things to tell him.
Come on. -Come on.
Holofira. Take this.
Look, you are pregnant. You need to eat more.
No, I'm full now. This is enough.
Thank you, Gonca. -My Holofira.
Look, Gonca is right. You eat
like a bird. You need to eat more.
And our child, our child
shouldn't starve, right?
Right...
And if it takes after my brother
it will need twice as much.
Look at him, my Bey. Look
at him, look at what he says.
Everyone knows how hungry you are, Alaeddin.
You're exaggerating, brother. When
did you ever see me eat that much?
May Allah grant both of us
to raise our children together.
Aameen. -Aameen.
May Allah let us be united and in peace forever.
Together with our children,
and our grandchildren,
...may we gather again at
such tables, God willing.
God willing.
You really started forgetting about me!
You used to say I was the one who
made you happy around this table, father!
But you grew up, my Fatma.
You are becoming an aunt.
-Right, sister.
Now you won't be jealous of
your niece/nephew, will you?
No.
My daughter will not grow up, right, Fatma?
Give me your hand, give
me your hand, my daughter!
Come on.
My daughter...
Walk.
You are making me confused.
Meryem.
My daughter, are you alright?
Are you full? Why did you leave?
I have a headache...
Come...
What do you think to make
your head ache like that, huh?
If it weren't for you...
..I would have died.
Osman Bey and...
..you..
..as if I was your own child...
...you saved me.
You are already our child.
All the children of the
Kayi are our own, Meryem.
Go, have some rest.
My Bey...
But I am not a Kayi.
I am not Meryem.
I am Poena.
I will tell my aunt your location.
My Bey...
What happened? What is wrong?
I am alright, thanks to Yusuf, my Bey.
I owe my life to him.
My Bey, I have things to tell you.
Come on then, let's go into the tent.
Put out the fires before evening.
You say Yusuf isn't a traitor
like his sister, huh, Saruca?
If he hadn't opened this wound in my chest
...both Yusuf and I would be dead now, my Bey.
"There is a wolf in the jackal's den now."
"I'm at my Bey's service", he said.
His sister is fork-tongued like a snake
but Yusuf is just the opposite, huh?
May Allah be pleased with him.
Aameen.
-Aameen.
Do you think Ulugan and traitor
Ilbay will trust Yusuf's words?
Maybe not in Kayi Tribe, but he has
influence in their own tribe, my Bey.
Begum Hatun let Yusuf
take over the chair of
Kecilisahs in return for
pledging loyalty to Ilbay.
So... As they bowed against Mongolians earlier.
...Tribe of Kecilisah isn't under
Mongolians' command anymore, you say
That's right, my Bey.
How will we make contact with Yusuf?
Did you agree on a method?
He'll check the hole of the huge
tree near Serinsu at times, my Bey.
We'll place your orders there.
God willing.
Good. Good.
I should send a message to my aunt to meet.
I wish there were another
way but I have to do this.
I will take revenge.
You like Meryem, not Poena.
-Boran.
-My Bey.
Give this to Aykurt. He'll take
it where Saruca mentioned.
-So Yusuf can follow my orders.
-Brother.
I can deliver it, my Bey.
What's your plan, my Bey? What
will Yusuf do in the tribe for us?
As Tribe of Kecilisah isn't
under Mongolians' command
...Yusuf will take his alps on our side
without drawing Ulugan and Ilbay's attention.
This will be the first and most
important step of our resurrection move.
It's important that the elders,
children and hatuns use swords.
But what we really need
is strong and brave alps.
Then what, my Bey?
Let's say we found alps.
What would alps need? Orhan, tell me.
Swords, arrows, bows,
catapults, and flying flame.
-They need any kind of weapons, my Bey.
-Yes.
Our best swords were...
...in the nearby outposts
that were protecting the tribe.
Mongolian dogs seized them, my Bey.
We won't only raid the outpost
and take our fine swords, Boran.
But we'll also break Mongolian
resistance around the tribe.
Alaaddin
Let's say both alps and swords are provided.
What else do we need?
-We need intelligence, my Bey.
-Intelligence, yes.
First, we should be awake.
And but we need to put heathens to sleep.
While alps collect information all around
...they'll also spread wrong
information about our whereabouts.
This duty belongs to Kanyumaz.
Alaaddin.
Inform him about his duty.
Tell me, Bala.
Do you have anything to
say? What else should we do?
We should give Turks a hope, my Bey.
Before anything else,
we need to place hopes in
the hearts of beys and
people under our command.
Right.
Turks have solid hearts and unbreakable faith.
We'll spread fear against heathens...
...but faith and hope in
the hearts of our people.
-God willing, my Bey.
-God willing.
For my son, my Bey.
For my son.
I'm disobeying you.
Deliver the note at any cost.
I'll take Ghazi and be back.
-Cerkutay Bey!
-Come on.
Brother.
Where did Cerkutay Bey go in the dark?
Come on.
First, we need to take the weapons.
When we complete the preparations.
...we will split up before the dawn.
-And we'll raid all the outposts.
-As you order, my Bey.
As you order, my Bey.
-Do I have permission, my Bey?
-Come in!
Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you too.
- Peace be upon you too.
-Didn't Cerkutay tell you about your duty?
-No, my Bey.
I'm here about Cerkutay Bey.
He rode off in the dark
without telling anyone anything.
My Bey, he must have gone to the tribe.
He'll both deliver the message to Yusuf and...
-And save Ghazi.
He risked..
...both his duty and his life, huh?
Forgive me, my Bey.
I need to save Ghazi, my precious
in this life, from those dastards.
Every moment he is there, my
breath is tearing my lungs apart.
It bleeds my heart.
Meryem.
-Why don't you sleep? -I couldn't.
Rest a bit more. We have
much to do in the morning.
You need to gain strength. Come on.
Who is that?
Cerkutay Bey.
Thanks to Allah.
-Yusuf Bey.
-My Bey.
-Saruca told us what you said.
-That's right.
I'm at Osman Bey's service.
I say I'm at Osman Bey's
service. Don't you trust me?
My Bey sent this.
Okay.
You should gather your
alps and make them join us.
Alright. I'll gather the alps
quickly. Let my Bey know.
My son.
Have you seen Ghazi? Is he alright?
He's fine. Don't worry.
Altuga keeps him in his tent.
He says he'll raise him as a Mongolian.
He thinks he can take
revenge from me in this way.
-I won't let that happen.
-Cerkutay Bey, wait.
If they see you in the
tribe, they won't let you live.
You will only deal with
the duty my Bey gave you!
Cerkutay Bey, don't do this.
You're our only spy left.
If I get exposed,
...don't do anything to risk your duty.
Even if I die.
This is my personal matter.
-May Allah help you.
-May He help all of us.
Go do your duty now.
My Bey, they are too many.
They protect the tribe from
that spot, my Shahzade.
That's why all those dogs gathered here.
What brings victory isn't numbers.
It is bravery and mind.
We will divide them now.
-Aykurt is waiting for our call. Samil?
-My Bey.
-Prepare the whistle arrow.
-As you order, my Bey.
Come on, brothers! Make those dogs follow you.
We're under attack!
We're under attack! Catch them!
-It's time to attack now.
-Come on, alps!
Allah is the greatest!
Cerkutay will save Ghazi, right?
God willing.
God willing, Ulgen.
But what Cerkutay Bey is doing isn't right.
He made a mistake by disobeying Osman Bey.
But they will back alive with Allah's will.
God willing.
I hope they come back alive.
-He ask for forgiveness later.
-God willing.
We're done. But you're still picking up herbs.
Praise be to my beautiful girl. Let me see it.
They are very nice.
Praise be.
Well... Where is Meryem?
Meryem..
She was picking up herbs with us.
Didn't she come here?
No, she didn't.
Mother.
Maybe, the kid got lost in the woods.
Alps!
Look for Meryem in the woods. Come on!
I told her to stick with us.
I hope she's not in trouble.
God willing, she isn't. Let's go.
Little bird.
Aunt.
Sending news with the innkeeper?
Deliver this letter to Sofia carefully, alright?
It's important.
-A genius idea. You're very smart.
-Aunt.
Thank God, you're alright.
What if they notice your absence?
We were picking up herbs in the woods.
They think I got lost.
You little demon.
-Well... What other news?
There's a traitor among you, aunt.
Yusuf.
He's gathering alps for Osman.
Damn it.
I knew I shouldn't have trusted Turks.
Alright.
Where is Osman hiding now?
In the forest behind Karain.
Poena.
Osman is going to die thanks to your help.
Don't stay there, alright?
Ulugan will let nobody live.
Lukas doesn't let anyone live either, aunt.
He almost killed me.
-Lukas?
-Lukas.
I will make him pay for this.
Osman and Bala saved me right in time.
What about your headaches?
Can you sleep more easily now?
No, aunt.
I have nightmares again.
Don't worry.
I've brought your medicine.
-What would I do without you, aunt?
-Take it.
-Someone's coming.
-Meryem Hatun!
Put swords, spears, flying flames
and everything else on the cart!
Hay Praise be.
My Bey, we will gain a victory
with these swords God willing.
God willing.
But our goal is not only to win the war.
First..
...it is to win Allah's mercy first.
Infidelity will be ended for sure.
Infidels will be destroyed.
But...
...we will not be the only ones to win.
The one that wins...
..will be Islam.
God willing my Bey. -God willing.
Come on.
Get ready. We are leaving.
-Alps!
Bring the horses, come on!
Neither your nokers(Mongolian Soldiers)...
...nor Byzantium's knights.
None of them found a single trace of Osman.
Your men..
What is it, Ilbay Bey?
Are you afraid because Osman
might come and take your throne?
Know your limits, Lukas.
Ilbay Bey is right about his concern.
If Osman returns and sits on the throne...
...he will be stronger than before.
Then, we won't be the only
ones who will lose their heads.
You are in my shadow, Hatun.
Those who live under my shadow...
...cannot be afraid of anyone but me.
We cannot find Osman.
He will come himself.
How will that happen?
I will hurt him badly.
I will tear apart the homeland...
...he holds dear, more than his own life.
You..
Lukas.
You want to take back the castles
Osman took from the Byzantine, don't you?
Right, Commander Ulugan.
Choose three castles.
Then inform us
I will give you the castles
you chose and their people.
You can turn them into slaves...
..or sell them.
You decide.
How can I show my gratitude to you, Ulugan?
You will pay a tax.
A heavy tax.
Sure.
The land you gave to the
Byzantines is my property, Ulugan.
You are..
...under my rule as well.
Your tent..
...your tribe...
..every breath you take...
...is my gift to you.
Don't forget whose door you serve at.
Then..
...your life and rule will be long.
Osman will come here...
...when he hears that...
...land has been taken from his state...
...and his people have become slaves again.
And he will be at the end of our chains again.
Red Devil.
What's this hurry for, Hatun?
I know where Osman is hiding.
Nokers(Mongolian Soldiers)!
Prepare the horses. We will go and hunt.
They will attack.
I need to inform my Bey.
I will take Ghazi and then go.
You..
Cerkutay.
You came to take your little dog, huh?
Begum Hatun's brother Yusuf.
He is a traitor.
He fooled us all Ulugan.
What are you saying, you infidel?
Why do you slander my brother?
Yusuf did not kill Saruca, Begum.
He tricked us.
Now their plan is...
...to place the Kecilisah Alps
you gave to his command...
...on Osman's side.
Traitor...
So his allegiance was not real.
-No.
My brother would not betray me!
-Shut up!
Hatun..
Shut up..
Shut up...
...so you won't share the
same fate with your brother.
Most importantly...
...I found the place that Osman is hiding.
Without wasting time..
...we must attack.
You couldn't have given
better news than this, Sofia.
How did you find that out?
You might be luring us into a trap.
I told you I have a spy near Osman.
The intelligence is correct.
Let's set out.
Now..
...who will save you from my hands, Osman?
We are leaving.
Lukas..
Thanks to my Poena who you tried to kill...
...we found Osman.
-Don't you ever...
I will not touch your precious daughter.
But what if she remembers?
It's not possible.
The potion I gave her
took away all her memories.
I will not leave my hat.
Ghazi! Ghazi!
Who are you? Father?
-Yes, your father! You are quite heavy handed.
How did you come here?
Ghazi, we are leaving!
Ghazi, we are leaving, come on!
The demons are coming! -He went to his son.
The demons are coming. Come on!
This place.
Come on.
Come on!
Come on father! Come on!
Father! -Are you alright?
-I am alright!
My lion, let's go!
So you have come to my arms, huh, brother?
You weren't this foolish when you were a Mongol.
Your problem is with me.
Not with my son.
Aren't children the heirs
of their fathers, brother?
Just as you betrayed your
father and your lineage..
...Ghazi will do the same to you.
My only concern is to...
...make you experience what
you made others experience.
I will never betray my Osman Bey or my father!
Don't you even dream about that, uncle!
I will take Ghazi out of the tribe.
Then I will come and surrender.
That's what I want.
He is just a child. -That's better.
He will meet the truth at a young age.
Ghazi run! -Nokers(Mongolian Soldiers)!
Father! Father!
Father! Let me go!
Father!
Let me go!
Father! Father!
Drop your sword, brother. Surrender.
You don't want your child die before you.
-Let me go!
Don't, father!
Father, let me die! You must not die, father!
Osman Bey needs you!
Don't, father!
Father, don't drop your swords!
Don't! Run away!
Father, what did you do?
Father! Father!
You are on the wrong way Altuga.
You are on the wrong way.
Spend the last moment with your child, brother.
The last.
Then..
...you will see how I turn him into your enemy.
I will kill you while you are alive.
You won't die easily.
You will regret that you didn't kill me!
Even if you are my brother...
...you will die the same
way Ulugan and his dogs die.
I will cut you into pieces.
I swear.
Alright.
Nokers(Mongolian Soldiers).
Take these two to the caged tent, come on!
No, no, father! Father! -I am with you my lion!
Let us go!
My Bey!
Are you going to tell me about Cerkutay?
Yes my Bey.
I know Cerkutay did something bad.
But he did it to save his son, my Bey.
-Boran.
Isn't his son our son?
Didn't we say we are going to
save Ghazi when the time comes?
This thing he did...
This thing he did put
us into a difficult position.
Cerkutay Bey...
...Cerkutay Bey knows Mongols, my Bey.
For sure they will come back safe and sound.
I know, my son. I know.
I trust him about that.
Alaeddin. -My Bey.
We now have enough ammunition.
-So you succeeded, huh?
-Thanks to Allah, my Bey.
We have pierced the heart of
the Mongol infidel with black steel.
Thank you my son.
Come on valiants! Let's ride!
Osman Bey Secret Tents
I walked away to gather more herbs.
Then I lost you.
We were worried about you, my Meryem daughter.
Look, Mongols are everywhere.
Don't do it again it's dangerous.
It won't happen again, Bala Hatun.
My beautiful daughter.
Let me see... Are you full now?
You helped us in our hardest moment.
If it weren't for you, my daughter
and I would be miserable.
Come on now, go to your mother.
Your daughter and you are...
...the trust of our Allah.
May Allah keep you together.
You can stay here as long as you want.
I appreciate, Bala Hatun.
Sisters will show you where you will stay.
Have some rest. Go.
But they are infidels..
-My daughter...
-Why are you helping them?
-They are human too.
They are human, even if they are Christians.
Right?
But...
Stop, my daughter.
Come here.
In the name of Allah,
the merciful, the compassionate.
We learned mercy for every being from our
Prophet (PBUH), who is a mercy to the worlds.
Look what I'll tell you.
When our Rasulullah Efendi (PBUH)...
...was sitting with his sahabas..
...a non-Muslim funeral passed in front of them.
And our Prophet stood up right away.
-Why?
People of the Prophet asked, as you did.
"Hey the Messenger of Allah,
he was a non-Muslim.
Why are we standing up?"
The Messenger of Allah said "Still, wasn't
he human?" and waited until the funeral passed...
...showed respect, even if
the deceased was non-Muslim.
But we are fighting.
Aren't we in this state because of them now?
These are two different things, my daughter.
We draw our sword against
those who show hostility
to us, who attacks us,
our wealth, and our faith.
Otherwise, we do not oppress anyone, regardless
of their language, religion, or race.
Especially children, women, and
the oppressed are valuable for us.
There are times when no sword
can defeat the power of mercy.
Do not forget this, alright, my daughter?
Come on.
Thanks to Allah! Osman Bey, welcome!
Thanks to Allah, Osman Bey!
Welcome! -Thank you. Thank you!
Thank you.
O people!
Our swords, which are the
hope of resurrection, have arrived.
Come on. Aykurt. -My Bey!
-Take these somewhere safe.
-As you order, my Bey.
Come on!
Bala. -My Bey...
Mother...
Mother, what are you doing?
What are you doing? Stop. Why are you
carrying this when there are so many men here?
Take this.
What is carrying this
burden for this state? We
would even give our
lives holding our swords.
My Osman Bey.
Mother..
This state is strong thanks to you.
Thanks to the valiants who run after me...
...and to mothers who
gave birth to those valiants!
Thank you mother.
Nothing will happen to this state, for sure.
We are a nation that
doesn't hesitate to sacrifice
anything, to be free,
and to be strong, my Bey.
The oppression of the infidels will not be
able to defeat the efforts of these mothers.
Yes, my Bala.
We will rise with our teeth, our nails,
our blood, and our lives, for sure.
God willing!
And together, we will grow the
fire of resurrection, God willing.
God willing my Bey!
Allah is the Greatest!
Begum Hatun Tents
My Alps!
My Beys, my valiants!
Tell me!
What does an Alp live for?
-Why does he fight with his sword?
-For the truth!
For war!
For customs!
Tell me!
Is this the right way? Are we going to...
...work with traitors and those who are sold?
Will we unite with those who declare
war on the da'wah of Almighty Allah?
Does this suit an Alp?
My Alps...
My valiants...
Will you ally with those
who sell the Hereafter in this world...
....a world we cannot
even control for a moment?
Will we remain silent and
be like the mute devils?
Or will we unite with Osman
Bey, who rebels against the tyranny...
...and bring this
treacherous sultanate to an end?
Tell me!
-Are you with me?
-We are with you!
Allah is the Greatest!
This is the best day to rebel
against the cruel! Attack!
Burn down their tribe!
Show mercy for nobody!
You will pay for this, Lukas!
By taking Osman's side, you chose death!
You're all alone, Yusuf!
Don't fight in vain.
Nobody is going to help you!
The tribe of Osman you trust
so much will be all destroyed!
Near Osman Bey Secret Tents
Burn down everything and
leave no heads over shoulders.
Osman, his people and family shouldn't survive.
As you order. Commander Ulugan.
But Olcaytu Khan...
Olcaytu...
...will get the news that
Byzantine killed Osman.
Let's bury Osman, his family
and everyone in the pit of hell.
-Here we go.
-Nokers(Mongolian Soldiers).
Ilbay.
I don't want my brother to die like this.
His betrayal has been exposed, Begum.
If we stand with him,
Ulugan won't let us live either.
It's only you and me now.
You should know this.
I will never leave you.
Come on.
Your alps and people are
going to die because of you!
They're going to die for their cause and
homeland instead of dying as traitors at least!
For nothing.
I would kill me if I were you, Lukas.
Who do you think you are?
You're a loser pretending to be
a bey under his sister's shadow.
What are you talking about?
-Get off!
-Hristo!
-Don't kill him.
-As you order. Commander.
Don't kill the survivors.
You'll wait for your turn, Yusuf.
But I'll give you that.
You will be very useful though you're a loser.
Whatever your goal is, you
won't be able to succeed!
Get off!
I'm not taking your filthy life...
...so you will be a lesson for
Osman's rebellious Beys and people.
Who do you think you are? Huh?
In the arena.
...you and your alps are going
to die in front of all people!
And everybody...
...will see Lukas' power...
...and that Kayi is done.
You think you can get away with this?
You dogs.
We've been dreaming of this day, Sofia.
Now it will be as we always desired.
-Look everywhere!
-Come on!
Osman... Where have you gone, Osman?
Altuga, what's going on?
There's nobody left in the
tribe. Commander Ulugan.
-They're all here, my Bey.
-Let them come.
-They're coming to their death.
-Vile dogs.
It seems Osman knew we were coming.
Sofia's spy betrayed
-They must have left some trails. Search!
-Nokers(Mongolian Soldiers)!
Alaaddin, you will shoot first.
Trap
-Now.
-This is a trap!
Praise be.
Nokers(Mongolian Soldiers) are coming, my Bey.
Here we go.
They'll be here shortly. Let's join the hatuns.
Come on.
Meryem.
We're lucky, you noticed them.
Or it would have been a disaster for us.
What have I done?
If Mongolians come
...they will kill everyone again.
Everyone.
What are you doing, mother?
-Give it to me.
-Thank you.
-Bala Hatun. Bala Hatun.
-Yes, dear?
What's the matter?
You look pale.
I was going to tell you
something but I'm afraid.
Tell me.
I'm not sure, but...
...I felt like someone was
behind me when I got lost.
Mongolians may have seen me.
What if they find us?
I should inform Osman Bey quickly.
Aunt...
Forgive me.
-Holofira.
-Sister-in-law.
Are you alright?
My girl?
I'm fine. I just felt some pain there.
I'm good now.
You ran. It must be why.
Bring a chair! You should sit down.
Osman Bey's coming.
-Is everyone alright?
-My girl...
-My Bey.
-Holofira, my dear.
Holofira... What happened, mother?
-Are you alright?
-I'm fine now. Don't worry.
She's fine. She just felt
some pain when she ran.
“Are you alright?
-I'm good.
What about Mongolians, my Bey?
My girl, thanks to your carefulness,
...we've got rid of Mongolians
for now. Thank you.
What now, father?
We'll find somewhere to stay now.
But we won't worry and give up.
We showed them our fist.
Now we'll get more powerful and be back.
They must have started tracking,
father. We should get away.
Come on, pack up your things. Come on, Holofira.
-Alright. Let's go, girl.
-Come on.
Come to me. Let's go.
People, get up. Time to go.
-Here we go.
-Come here, girl.
Begum Hatun.
-Ilbay.
Begum Hatun. Begum Hatun.
Begum Hatun! Begum Hatun!
Are you alright?
-My arm...
I can't move my arm.
Don't worry. I'll take you to a healer.
We'd be dead if you hadn't
noticed. You saved us all.
I swear..
Osman.
I swear I will skin you!
I swear!
Nobody in your family will survive!
May high beech trees be my witness!
I swear on my ancestor Genghis...
I swear I won't stop before I kill you!
I swear!
Osman Bey Secret Tents
Come on, man. Do it properly.
Come on, brothers.
Carry the chests.
We should secure the weapons first.
This place won't be exposed, God willing, my Bey.
It won't be, Bala.
Warn Meryem and all people, though.
The enemy are watching
us. So we need to be careful.
Nobody will leave the
tribe without my knowledge.
Orhan. Alps.
-My Bey.
-Kanyumaz.
Kanyumaz?
What? Important news?
Yes, my Bey.
The intelligence we've collect...
The news isn't good at all.
Cerkutay Bey...
Yes?
He got caught when he tried
to save his son Ghazi, my Bey.
They're keeping in a cage tent in the tribe now.
What are you saying, Kanyumaz?
First my son and now my husband...
-My Allah, help me...
-Ulgen, stand strong.
They'll be alright.
We'll save both Cerkutay and Ghazi.
Help me, my Allah.
You obviously important news.
-Follow me, Kanyumaz.
-As you order, my Bey.
-What are you doing, Ulugan?
-You sent me to death.
My nokers(Mongolian Soldiers) died.
Your spy betrayed us.
What are you talking about?
There was nobody when we reached the tribe.
They knew we were going there.
-No.
She would never tell.
Ulugan, she would never do that.
Are you sure you didn't get followed?
How do you know our spy betrayed you?
Osman's spies are everywhere.
Commander Ulugan, they raided
the outpost protecting the tribe.
Kayi people attacked and
collected all the weapons.
I broke Osman's wings.
But it didn't work!
I burned his tent.
It didn't work.
He's still rising against
me with just a few raiders.
Well..
I arrested your treacherous
brother, Begum Hatun.
Tomorrow, in the arena, we're
going to kill Yusuf and his alps...
...in front of Osman's Beys and
people to make an example for everyone!
From now on, everybody will know...
Whoever stands with Osman is going to die!
It will be a massacre.
We'll destroy Osman's ideal.
It will be a huge massacre.
Kanyumaz, what's the situation?
I don't like saying this, my Bey, but...
...Ulugan will give three castles in our
land to Byzantine which Lukas will choose.
They're trying to eat our
flesh like vultures, huh?
What about the traitor called Ilbay, my Bey?
He says he's the bey of
Kayi but kneels before them!
Well... I have things to tell him as well.
But lion's meat tastes bitter.
It won't bu hunted by jackals easily.
We will show them.
My Bey, I also have news about Yusuf Bey.
Yusuf Bey and alps of Kecilisah
who intended to join us...
..got attacked by Lukas and Sofia.
What are you saying, Kanyumaz?
How did they know about our plan?
Whenever we take a step.
...they always know about it.
Obviously, there is a spy among us.
But all the people here suffered
from Mongolians, my Bey.
Who would spy for Ulugan and why?
When I find out, I will cut
off his head personally.
Tell me, Kanyumaz. Where are
they keeping Yusuf and the alps?
My Shahzade, Lukas has sent them to the arena.
They're going to be executed before Turkish
and Roman people and our Beys tomorrow.
I know what they intend to do.
They want to spread terror in hearts.
They want to extinguish our resurrection fire.
But don't worry.
We won't let that happen.
Thanks to Allah.
Osman Bey is saved.
He didn't get tricked by those snakes.
Father.
We will survive too, right?
-Ghazi, my son... We will.
For sure, we will survive.
We always do.
You're right.
Look at me. What Altuga said
didn't discourage you, right?
Of course not!
I'm the son of Double-Sworded Cerkutay Bey!
Praise be to my boy!
You're truly Cerkutay Bey's son.
Okay, but...
I haven't eaten anything for days.
Just be patient, my boy.
We will eat soon. Your father
will get a feast prepared for you.
I'll tell your mother to prepare a long table.
A day long with a horse!
You will sit alone there.
And me of course. We
will join in the middle and...
I'm not a cruel man who
would make his nephew starve.
Come.
Their meat is not like ours.
Your uncle forgot his humanity
from eating pork, my son.
We don't want your food.
We don't want it.
Ghazi will eat like a Mongol.
He will become a Mongol.
He will not be a traitor a Muslim dog like you.
A Muslim never eats pork! Never!
Even if I die of hunger, I won't eat it.
Never!
Did you get your answer?
As you wish, Ghazi noker(Mongolian soldier).
I am not a noker!
Let's see how long you can resist.
I am not!
My lion. My valiant.
You gave him the answer he deserved! My valiant!
Ghazi.
-Do you want to wrestle?
-Yes.
Allah!
-I won!
-No, you didn't. You didn't win.
My Bala..
Because of the spy among us...
...no one except the Beys
and Shahzades will go outside.
Don't worry, my Osman.
You say there's no choice but to go to the
arena to light the fire of resurrection, huh?
Yusuf and the Alps...
I will never leave them there.
I know, my Osman, but Ulugan, Lukas,
Sofia... all are waiting to hunt you...
...but you still want to go, huh?
-Look my Bala.
Land can be lost. Lives can be lost. But...
...if we don't go after those valiants
who are ready to give their lives for us...
...then hope will be lost.
One who does not have hope has no homeland.
No one knows this better than those devils.
That's why they want to leave us alone.
They want to leave us helpless.
They want to kill those
around us as a lesson to others.
No.
I will never allow that.
I will light the fire of Kayi's resurrection...
...in front of those infidels in their arena.
Brother..
Why did you come? You
should've gone to your husband.
Why did you do this to us, brother?
Why did you do it, sister?
You betrayed Osman Bey and
your state. Why did you do it?
They will kill you. They
will kill everyone here.
Even if we die, we will die with honor.
But you, as a traitor...
What happened to your arm?
Are you alright?
I am telling you that you are going to die!
Are you still worried about me?
From now on, you don't
have a brother to protect you.
Take care of yourself, sister.
Begum.
-Don't let Ulugan see you here.
-You traitor dog!
It's all because of you! You tricked
my sister, everything is because of you!
The real traitor is you, Yusuf.
You betrayed both your sister and me.
If you were with us...
I'd rather die with honor than
stand next to a dog like you, Ilbay!
You are a dog who betrayed
your state, your lineage!
But don't worry. You'll pay for all of it.
You will!
You will pay for it!
Find a way.
Save my brother.
Your brother does not bow down, Begum.
There is no way out from this.
Let's go before someone sees us.
Come on! Come on!
Shut up and be quick.
The show you are about to watch
will never leave your small minds.
Come on.
Shameless dog.
It will never leave their minds, huh?
I will leave no mind in you.
Be patient, Boran Bey.
Come on come on!
A simple death is not enough for these dogs.
We will show that a wolf
does not bow to a jackal.
We will destroy their idols of arrogance.
Their heads will be crushed
under those idols today.
Look at their end.
This is the end of those who stand with Osman.
If there's anyone who still sees him
as a savior, he should look at his end.
Even Osman cannot escape
the cold edge of my sword.
Is your little bird...
...still loyal to you?
Maybe she is the reason
Osman is still alive today.
Poena would never betray me, Lukas.
She's closer to me than
anyone else, I'm her only support.
Still, be careful
If our plan fails one more
time. I'll know it's because of her.
Lukas.
I didn't kill her on the cliff that day.
But I swear, if it happens again...
I will kill her.
I can't witness this, Ilbay.
Even if he's a traitor, I don't
want to see my brother like this.
Don't you argue about it.
Take the Alps with you. Be careful.
Dastard dogs.
They've already taken the front
seat for the massacre they'll do.
They'll carry both their sins
and their punishments together.
Everyone knows their duty.
So, you prepared this for my valiants, huh?
This place will be your nightmare.
Osman Bey Secret Tent
Forgive me, aunt.
How will I give it to her now?
Meryem.
Take these to Bala Hatun.
I should not go now.
Why?
It's been ten years..
She hasn't cooked this meal
since Halime passed away.
Come, my daughter.
Bala Hatun, your arm must be tired, let me help.
No, thank you, my daughter.
I keep myself busy this way.
I am worried about Osman Bey and the children.
Their duty is very hard.
May Allah help them.
It smells good, right?
It smells really good.
It is a very familiar smell.
What dish is this?
It's As soup.
But the secret is in the herbs inside.
Its smell reminds me of many memories.
I haven't made it in a long time.
When I saw those herbs, I decided to make it.
-I wonder if my mother used to cook it too.
-She probably did.
This is a Turkish soup.
My little daughter used to love it so much.
I never cooked it after she was gone.
My Halime...
...loved its smell.
Even though she was tiny, she'd
eat more than she was supposed to.
Be careful, don't burn your mouth.
My Halime would rush and burn herself.
Mother, it's delicious. Blow on it, it's hot.
Slow down, my daughter, you'll burn yourself.
It's very hot but smells so good.
Your hands touched those herbs.
That's why this soup is so good.
Wait, you'll burn your mouth.
Mother?
Forgive me, brother.
If I hadn't been exiled from the
tribe, none of this would've happened.
Bala, Gonca... they'll both pay the price.
They are the reason for my betrayal.
And I'll be the reason for their death.
You..
Turks with broken wings,
who have lost your freedom.
And you, foolish Greeks
who bowed down to Osman...
...even though he ruined your lands.
All this preparation in the square is for you.
Today, you will watch the end of
the state you sacrificed your lives for.
Your Osman Bey, who dragged
you to death, is gone now!
Your free and powerful state does not exist!
I see that you don't even
have the strength to fight back.
Soon..
Soon, the scene you'll watch
will be a lesson for all of you.
Hristo.
Bring Osman's loyal Alps.
This arena will echo with the screams of
those who speak his name and follow his cause.
Lukas.
Today this arena..
...will be echoed with your screams, Lukas.
-Are you a man?
-What is he doing here?
He has a death wish. Nokers(Mongolian Soldiers)!
Stop, stop!
As Osman has come to his death himself.
...let's hear his final words.
We'll see if you are a man or not.
To show your strength against my people and beys
...you organized this execution, huh?
Alright, alright.
Here we go.
Do you have a heart for this?
Fight me if you do. Huh?
One-one-one fight.
I'm putting forward my own
life in return for my alps' lives.
You have a heart for this?
Those who you hide behind
and work together with...
Anyone can fight me.
You need to finish our interrupted fight, huh?
I will kill you before people
with pleasure, Osman.
Draw back!
Bring my shield.
-Give him too.
-I don't want a shield.
Do you think...
...this shield can protect you from my wrath?
We kept you waiting. You must be bored.
Don't worry. All of you
are going to die shortly.
Soldiers, prepare them.
Chain their feet and bring them to the arena.
Stupid Lukas.
No need for a fight. Just kill him.
Even if Osman win
...he can't get out of here alive.
Look around.Turn around and look.
These are your last seconds.
This is the end..
...for those like you who
brought oppression in these lands.
This is your last day.
You'll wish you had never come here today.
-Come on, my Bey!
-Come on!
Come on, my Bey?
Get off! We aren't cowards!
We'll walk even if the way leads to death! Alps!
Get your heads up! Death is glorious for us!
I just pray to Almighty Allah that He won't
let those dastards be happy with our deaths!
Move! You're going to die but still talking!
Stop there.
Only Allah decides who dies first.
O Allah
My Bey? Orhan Bey.
Alaaddin Bey, Boran Bey.
How did you get in here?
Spread your arms.
Where is Osman Bey? What is he doing?
They think they can trick us.
Let them play.
They want to slaughter my Beys and alps.
So they will spread terror in hearts.
Don't worry.
-They won't succeed.
-My Bey.
What is our plan?
Well..
I will stall Lukas in the fighting area.
Then..
All the eyes will be on us.
And will save the alps and Yusuf in the back.
Exactly, son.
But..
Father, you will be alone.
That's too dangerous.
-You may be hurt. -Alaaddin.
You can't be Egypt's Sultan
before you fall into the pit.
Don't worry.
We will ruin their plans.
-God willing, my Bey.
-God willing.
-We will.
Osman is fighting on his own for us, huh?
Yes. We need to get out of here quickly.
-My father can't stall him any longer.
-It's hard to get out of here.
But not impossible.
Alps! Brothers!
It's time to fight now.
-May Allah bless our fight.
-Aameen.
-Let's go!
-Let's go.
Hold on, my Bey!
Come on, Lukas.
I remember the first day I came to the
frontiers to stop a barbarian shepherd, Osman.
-Finally... Finally, this is it.
-You're right.
I'm a kind of shepherd.
But we don't herd pigs.
For Baysungur.
This is for Bayhan Bey and all the martyrs.
For the vengeance of my unborn grandchild.
Lukas.
This place...
...will be watered with your blood today.
Nokers(Mongolian Soldiers)!
I'm Osman Bey, Bey of Kayi!
I'm one of a thousand Turkish soldiers.
The dog who dishonored
my banner, harmed my state...
...and oppressed my innocent people...
...is under my feet now.
I swear on the land I step on, the sword I hold.
...and the lives I took for Allah's cause...
I swear that dastards like you...
Rats like you...
...will end up under my feet just like this dog.